<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>heal.lgbt on Queer Healing Resources</title>
    <link>https://heal.lgbt/</link>
    <description>Recent content in heal.lgbt on Queer Healing Resources</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://heal.lgbt/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>heal.lgbt disclaimer &amp; license</title>
      <link>https://heal.lgbt/disclaimer/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal.lgbt/disclaimer/</guid>
      <description>USE HEAL.LGBT AND THE INFORMATION CONTAINED HEREIN AT YOUR OWN RISK. INFORMATION ON THIS SITE MAY BE INCORRECT. HEAL.LGBT CANNOT GUARANTEE THE VALIDITY OF THE INFORMATION FOUND HERE.
The authors and contributors to this content cannot guarantee the validity of the information found here. Please make sure that you understand that the information provided here is being provided freely, and that no kind of agreement or contract is created between you and any persons associated with this content or project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>LGBT Crisis Resources</title>
      <link>https://heal.lgbt/fml/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal.lgbt/fml/</guid>
      <description>Are you in crisis? Many people have been through times that feel like the end. Where it seems like nothing will get better, ever. And when they come to the other side of it, they don&amp;rsquo;t even
If so, people want to help you. Whether you are scared for your own safety or just feeling lonely and you want someone to text with, you can reach out any time day or night.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>San Francisco resources</title>
      <link>https://heal.lgbt/docs/bayarea/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://heal.lgbt/docs/bayarea/</guid>
      <description>See also: SF LGBT Center Resources directory
Trauma-informed spiritual groups SF Dharma Collective
SF Zen Center
GLIDE radically inclusive church
(there are many more)
Immersion Learning &amp;amp; Retreat Centers 1440 Multiversity - Santa Cruz
Esalen Institute — Big Sur holistic alternative retreat center
Spirit Rock — Marin Insight meditation center
Green Gulch Farm — Marin
Deer Park Monastery — Escondido, CA — Thich Nhat Hanh’s monestary in the US
HIV/AIDS Support SF AIDS Foundation</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
